<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Release Notes on </title>
    <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Release Notes on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>zh-CN</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes For 3.0.0</title>
      <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v300/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v300/</guid>
      <description>How to get v3.0.0  Install KubeSphere v3.0.0 on Linux Install KubeSphere v3.0.0 on existing Kubernetes  Release Notes Installer FEATURES  A brand-new installer: KubeKey, v1.0.0, which is a turnkey solution to installing Kubernetes with KubeSphere on different platforms. It is more easy to use and reduces the dependency on OS environment  UPGRADES &amp;amp; ENHANCEMENTS  Be compatible with Kubernetes 1.15.x, 1.16.x, 1.17.x and 1.18.x for ks-installer, v3.0.0 KubeKey officially supports Kubernetes 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes For 2.1.1</title>
      <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v211/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v211/</guid>
      <description>KubeSphere 2.1.1 was released on Feb 23rd, 2020, which has fixed known bugs and brought some enhancements. For the users who have installed versions of 2.0.x or 2.1.0, make sure to read the user manual carefully about how to upgrade before doing that, and feel free to raise any questions on GitHub.
What&amp;rsquo;s New in 2.1.1 Installer UPGRADE &amp;amp; ENHANCEMENT  Support Kubernetes v1.14.x、v1.15.x、v1.16.x、v1.17.x，also solve the issue of Kubernetes API Compatibility#1829 Simplify the steps of installation on existing Kubernetes, and remove the step of specifying cluster&amp;rsquo;s CA certification, also specifying Etcd certification is no longer mandatory step if users don&amp;rsquo;t need Etcd monitoring metrics Backup the configuration of CoreDNS before upgrading  BUG FIXES  Fix the issue of importing apps to App Store  App Store UPGRADE &amp;amp; ENHANCEMENT  Upgrade OpenPitrix to v0.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes For 2.1.0</title>
      <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v210/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v210/</guid>
      <description>KubeSphere 2.1.0 was released on Nov 11th, 2019, which fixes known bugs, adds some new features and brings some enhancement. If you have installed versions of 2.0.x, please upgrade it and enjoy the better user experience of v2.1.0.
Installer Enhancement  Decouple some components and make components including DevOps, service mesh, app store, logging, alerting and notification optional and pluggable Add Grafana (v5.2.4) as the optional component Upgrade Kubernetes to 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes For 2.0.2</title>
      <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v202/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v202/</guid>
      <description>KubeSphere 2.0.2 was released on July 9, 2019, which fixes known bugs and enhances existing feature. If you have installed versions of 1.0.x, 2.0.0 or 2.0.1, please download KubeSphere installer v2.0.2 to upgrade.
What&amp;rsquo;s New in 2.0.2 Enhanced Features  API docs are available on the official website. Block brute-force attacks. Standardize the maximum length of resource names. Upgrade the gateway of project (Ingress Controller) to the version of 0.24.1. Support Ingress grayscale release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes For 2.0.1</title>
      <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v201/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v201/</guid>
      <description>KubeSphere 2.0.1 was released on June 9th, 2019.
Bug Fix  Fix the issue that CI/CD pipeline cannot recognize correct special characters in the code branch. Fix CI/CD pipeline&amp;rsquo;s issue of being unable to check logs. Fix no-log data output problem caused by index document fragmentation abnormity during the log query. Fix prompt exceptions when searching for logs that do not exist. Fix the line-overlap problem on traffic governance topology and fixed invalid image strategy application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release Notes For 2.0.0</title>
      <link>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v200/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://kubesphere-v3.netlify.app/zh/docs/release/release-v200/</guid>
      <description>KubeSphere 2.0.0 was released on May 18th, 2019.
What&amp;rsquo;s New in 2.0.0 Component Upgrades  Support Kubernetes Kubernetes 1.13.5 Integrate QingCloud Cloud Controller. After installing load balancer, QingCloud load balancer can be created through KubeSphere console and the backend workload is bound automatically.  Integrate QingStor CSI v0.3.0 storage plugin and support physical NeonSAN storage system. Support SAN storage service with high availability and high performance. Integrate QingCloud CSI v0.2.1 storage plugin and support many types of volume to create QingCloud block services.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>